Finding Aid for the Kenneth Rexroth Papers LSC.0175
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Printed materials, 1936-1976; 36 boxes (18 linear ft.).
  - Subseries 6A: Articles and essays,., 1946-1975; 3.5 boxes.
    - Proby, J.C.P., no date.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 25)
      "The Rolf Method of postural release and integration"
    - Public Structures, INC., 1965 February 1.; 2 items. (Box 112, Folder 26)
      "Report on the rehabilitation and modernization of San Francisco's War Memorial Cultural Center"
    - Quinn, Patrick J., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 27)
      "Real determinants of significant church building"
    - Rather, L.J., 1956-1974.; 10 items. (Box 112, Folder 28)
      Assorted reprints of articles and essays.
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--At Large., ca. 1974.; ca. 50 items. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--A., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--B., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--C., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--D., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--E., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--F., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--G., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--H., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--I., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--J-K., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--L., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--M., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--N., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--O., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--P., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--Q-R., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--S., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--T., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--U., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--V., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--W-Z., ca. 1955-1975.; ca. 25 items. (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Roditi, Edouard., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 11)
      "The making of Jews, or The inquisition in Portugal"
    - Rolf, Ida P., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 12)
      "Structural integration: gravity, an unexplored factor in a more human use of human beings"
    - Savage, D.S., 1947.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 13)
      "The mind of Virginia Woolf"
    - Sontag, Susan., 1969 February.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 14)
      Untitled article on Cuba.
    - Spender, Stephen., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 15)
      "The year's developments in the arts and sciences"
    - Stanford, Ann., 1969.; 4 items. (Box 114, Folder 16)
      Assorted poems and an essay introduction.
    - Theobald, Robert., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 17)
      "Cybernation, unemployment, and freedom"
    - Torrance, Robert., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 18)
      "Modes of being and time in the world of Godot"
    - Tyler, Parker., 1952.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 19)
      "Rashomon as modern art"
    - Van Ghent, Dorothy., no date.; 2 items. (Box 114, Folder 20)
      "The passion of the groves"
    - Viereck, Peter., 1949-1954.; 10 items. (Box 114, Folder 21)
      Assorted essays and publicity material
    - Von Ridelstein, Maria., 1966.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 22)
      "Will the works of abstract art be the dominating factor in the culture of the future?"
    - Wagner, Geoffrey., 1952 April.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 23)
      "The use of lallans for prose"
    - Wertheimer, R.G., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 24)
      "A concluding lecture in American economic history"
    - Wheelwright, Joseph., 1956.; 1 item. (Box 114, Folder 25)
      "Jung's psychological concepts"
    - Wolfe, Bertram D., 1946, 1967.; 2 items. (Box 114, Folder 26)
      "Das Kapital one hundred years later"; "The Russian intelligentsia"
  - Subseries 6B: Clippings and reviews,., 1936-1975; 3 boxes.
    Clippings on a variety of subjects, including reviews of Rexroth's work, courtesy of his clipping service. Arranged by original subject filing titles, with the exception of: reviews, which are further arranged by the title of the reviewed work; clippings about Rexroth, which have been further arranged in a chronological order. For two scrapbooks with additional clippings of reviews, see box 60.
    - Actor's Workshop., 1965.; ca. 25 items. (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Bay Guardian., 1970.; 4 items. (Box 115, Folder 2)
      Copies of clippings related to the San Francisco paper.
    - Beats., 1960 October 23.; 1 item. (Box 115, Folder 3)
      Clipping features a photo of Gary Snyder.
    - Civil rights., 1964.; 7 items. (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Ets-Hokin, Jeremy., 1965.; 4 items. (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Ginsberg, Allen., 1957 September.; 7 items. (Box 115, Folder 6)
      Scope and Content note
      Articles about the obscenity trial for Ginsberg's "Howl" and a photocopy of the original mimeograph. The original has been removed and added to the Bound Manuscripts collection, 170/736.
    - Miscellaneous., 1936-1975.; ca. 200 items. (Box 115, Folder 7-10)
      Miscellaneous newspapers and clippings with no mention of Rexroth.
    - Reviews--The Alternative Society., 1970. (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Reviews--American Poetry in the 20th Century., 1971. (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Reviews--The Art of Worldly Wisdom., 1954. (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Reviews--Assays., 1962. (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Reviews--An Autobiographical Novel., 1966. (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Reviews--Beyond the Mountains., 1951. (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Reviews--Bird in the Bush., 1959. (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Reviews--Classics Revisited., 1968-1969. (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Reviews--Collected Longer Poems of Kenneth Rexroth., 1969. (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Reviews--Collected Shorter Poems of Kenneth Rexroth., 1967. (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Reviews--Communalism., 1975. (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Reviews--The Dragon and the Unicorn., 1953. (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Reviews--The Elastic Retort., no date. (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Reviews--Fourteen Poems by O.V. De L. Miolsz., 1952. (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Reviews--The Green Child., 1949. (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Reviews--The Homestead Called Damascus., 1963. (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Reviews--In Defense of the Earth., 1957. (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Reviews--In What Hour., 1940. (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Reviews--Natural Numbers., 1964. (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Reviews--The New British Poets., 1949. (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Reviews--New Poems., 1975. (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Reviews--100 Poems from the Chinese., 1957-1965. (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Reviews--100 Poems from the French., 1972. (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Reviews--100 Poems from the Japanese., 1956. (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Reviews--The Orchid Boat., 1973. (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Reviews--Pierre Reverdy., 1972-1973. (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Reviews--Poems from the Greek Anthology., 1962. (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Reviews--The Phoenix and the Tortoise., 1944. (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - Reviews--The Residual Years., 1968. (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - Reviews--Selected Poems., 1948. (Box 116, Folder 30)
    - Reviews--The Signature of All Things., 1950. (Box 116, Folder 31)
    - Reviews--Sky Sea Birds Earth., 1972. (Box 116, Folder 32)
    - Reviews--30 Spanish Poems of Love and Exile., 1956. (Box 116, Folder 33)
    - Reviews--With Eye and Ear., 1971. (Box 116, Folder 34)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth., 1949-1973.; ca. 450 items. (Box 117, Folder 1-10)
      Assorted newspaper and magazine clippings that mention of Rexroth.
    - Student protest movements., 1960.; ca. 100 items. (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 6C: Ephemera,., 1940-1974; 10 boxes.
    Ephemeral materials from a variety of sources, particularly events, primarily from San Francisco in the 1960s. Arranged alphabetically by file title, which is either the creator name or the general topic of the contents. See box 159 for oversize materials such as publicity posters announcing readings by Rexroth, Ferlinghetti, Ginsberg, Snyder, and others.
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Triple Revolution., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 118, Folder 1)
      Pamphlet.
    - Advertising material., no date.; 38 items. (Box 118, Folder 2)
      Commercial advertising material sent to the Rexroths for assorted products and services.
    - Alternative Press., no date.; 4 items. (Box 118, Folder 3)
      Broadsides and poems by William Matthews, Diane di Prima and Joe Ribar.
    - American Conservatory Theater., 1969.; 2 items. (Box 118, Folder 4)
      Assorted printed materials.
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies., 1962.; 18 items. (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Aspen Music Festival., 1961.; 6 items. (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Awaji Puppet Theater of Japan., 1974.; 2 items. (Box 118, Folder 7)
      Programs for a UCSB performance.
    - Awards., 1962-1964.; 2 items. (Box 118, Folder 8)
      Who's Who certificate; humorous certificate signed by John Ciardi.
    - Berkeley Experimental Arts Foundation., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 118, Folder 9)
      Open theater and gallery program.
    - Bibliographies., 1948-1949.; 10 items. (Box 118, Folder 10)
      Assorted book lists on a variety of subjects.
    - Black Sparrow Press., ca. 1971.; 26 items. (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Bodega Head (Atomic Park)., 1962.; 3 items. (Box 118, Folder 12)
      Printed materials about the controversy, and a letter to the Sonoma County Board of Supervisors.
    - Bowery Press., 1969.; 5 items. (Box 118, Folder 13)
      Broadsides featuring the poetry of C.H. Hejinian, Tony Scibella and James Ryan Morris (broadsheets no. 4-6).
    - Bread Loaf Writers' Conference., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 118, Folder 14)
      Address list.
    - Cabrillo Music Festival., 1965, 1972.; 6 items. (Box 118, Folder 15)
      Featuring Carlos Chavez and Kenneth Rexroth.
    - California Arts Commission., 1965.; 3 items. (Box 119, Folder 1)
      Report to the governor; artists' protest of the Vietnam conflict; the palace of fine arts.
    - California Institute for the Arts., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 2)
      Course catalog materials.
    - Californians Against Absurd Censorship., 1966.; 6 items. (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs., 1970-1972.; 14 items. (Box 119, Folder 4)
      Assorted rare book catalogs.
    - Chinatown (San Francisco)., 1965.; 5 items. (Box 119, Folder 5)
      Printed materials.
    - Christian Brothers of California., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 6)
      Objects of wine in art: a historical collection of the Christian Brothers.
    - Chu-i, Po., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 7)
      Poems of Po Chu-I, translated by Frank W. Price.
    - Churches., 1953-1971.; ca. 20 items. (Box 119, Folder 8)
      Printed material from various churches.
    - Committee of Correspondence., 1960.; 3 items. (Box 119, Folder 9)
      Statement.
    - Composer's Forum., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 10)
      Index to bay area composers.
    - Conner, Bruce., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 11)
      Political flier.
    - Costanzo, Gerald., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 12)
      Rules for Being Dressed to Kill (broadside, Denver: Absynthe House).
    - Creative Arts Festival., 1969.; 3 items. (Box 119, Folder 13)
      Brochures.
    - Dailey, Joel., 1976.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 14)
      Booklet of poetry entitled First Crescent.
    - Dance Spectrum., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 15)
      Publicity materials stapled together, including an interview with Michelle Nichols.
    - Dan Theatre West., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 16)
      Proposal.
    - Dartington Hall., 1959.; 2 items. (Box 119, Folder 17)
      Brochure and letter.
    - Deleuze, Henri., 1958.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 18)
      Illustrated booklet of French poetry entitled Noel Otomi.
    - Di Suvero, V.M., no date.; 1 item. (Box 119, Folder 19)
      The Plague in Saigon (Polemic Publication no. 1, San Francisco: Protest Press).
    - Dining Club., 1963.; ca. 75 items. (Box 121, Folder 1)
      Response cards.
    - Events, fliers and programs (1-4 of 9)., ca. 1945-1970.; ca. 400 items. (Box 121, Folder 2-5)
      Announcements and ephemera related to conferences and local events, primarily dramatic productions, exhibitions, gatherings, and readings. See box 159 for publicity posters for readings by Rexroth, Snyder, Ferlinghetti, Ginsberg, and others.
    - Events, fliers and programs (5-9 of 9)., ca. 1945-1970.; ca. 500 items. (Box 122, Folder 1-5)
      Announcements and ephemera related to conferences and local events, primarily dramatic productions, exhibitions, gatherings, and readings.
    - Fine presses., ca. 1970.; ca. 50 items. (Box 123, Folder 1)
      Prospectuses, catalogs, cards and announcements from fine printers, including Red Hill Press, Cranium Press, Hoyem, etc.
    - Firrini, Vincent., no date.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 2)
      A voice remembered program.
    - Free City University., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Fund for a Free and Competitive Press., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 4)
      Open letter.
    - German theater., ca. 1966.; 10 items. (Box 123, Folder 5)
      Assorted programs. For additional German matierals, see Series 5, Subseries 5F (Travel).
    - Gott, Amos G., no date.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 6)
      A Portfolio of Drawings of Elkhart and Vicinity.
    - Great Slime Movement., 1952-1955.; 2 items. (Box 123, Folder 7)
      Graphic arts book published by the Flat Press; includes a letter from Dr. Bamshackled Crackslamer about the Great Slime Movement.
    - Greenwald, Ted., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 8)
      Blink (illustrated poem, New York: Buffalo Press).
    - Hippies., 1967.; 7 items. (Box 123, Folder 9)
      Clippings about hippies and a printed letter from Father Harris, pastor of the All Saint's Haight Ashbury parish.
    - Housing and urban planning., 1961.; 5 items. (Box 123, Folder 10)
      Printed material about housing developments in Islamabad, Baghdad, and Philadelphia.
    - Hunter Libertarian Alliance., 1974.; 3 items. (Box 123, Folder 11)
      Anarchist conference materials.
    - Hunter's Point Ministry of the Episcopal Church., 1966.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 12)
      Form letter.
    - Indiana Authors' Day., 1969.; 2 items. (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Indiana University., 1965.; 3 items. (Box 123, Folder 14)
      Pamphlets and alumni magazine.
    - Industrial Workers of the World., no date.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 15)
      Don't Scab! flier.
    - Information & Contacts., 1971.; 2 items. (Box 123, Folder 16)
      Geneva publication.
    - Isla Vista., 1970.; 7 items. (Box 123, Folder 17)
      Assorted open letters, fliers, and articles about the Santa Barbara riots.
    - Japonai Serie., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 18)
      Mimeographed booklet of Japanese-inspired poetry by students in Plainview, NY.
    - Japanese poets., 1969-1974.; 4 items. (Box 123, Folder 19)
      Small lithographed booklets of poetry by Arima Takashi, Yuzuru Katasiri, and Susumu Hasegawa.
    - Jeffers, Robinson., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 20)
      Reading checklist.
    - Kerrigan, Thomas., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 21)
      The Changeling (Malpelo broadside one, copy d/a-z), signed by the author.
    - KPFA (folder 1 of 2)., 1958-1969.; 12 items. (Box 123, Folder 22)
      Folios and station ephemera. Includes a front-cover feature on Rexroth.
    - KPFA (folder 2 of 2)., 1970-1972.; 12 items. (Box 124, Folder 1)
      Folios and station ephemera.
    - KPFK., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 2)
      Portfolio.
    - KRAB., 1972-1975.; 5 items. (Box 124, Folder 3)
      Postcards, broadcast calendar, and program guide.
    - Larsson, Raymond E.F., 1953.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 4)
      Poem for the wedding of Sandra Evelyn Winters and August Derleth.
    - Levy, D.A., 1967.; 5 items. (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Marie, Janet., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 6)
      Booklet of poetry entitled Heart's Chord.
    - McClure, Michael., no date.; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 7)
      Letter-press version of single poem, Komos, signed by the author; flier.
    - Membership cards and effects., 1953-1969.; 16 items. (Box 124, Folder 8)
      Assorted ID and membership cards, including medals for the Commonwealth Club of California.
    - Midwest Research Institute., 1961.; 4 items. (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Miner, Tom., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 10)
      Mimeographed booklet of poetry by Miner and Godolphin Reed entitled "Me, Wag."
    - Miscellaneous., ca. 1950s.; 9 items. (Box 124, Folder 11)
      Assorted printed materials, including a French songbook for Edith Paif's "La vie en rose", a Credo for Librarians, a list of interview questions (presumably for Rexroth) and small booklets by anonymous authors.
    - MIT Arts Commission., 1969.; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 12)
      Reports.
    - Moody, Reynolds., no date.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 13)
      Political pamphlet, "Pyramiding Echelons of Tens: A Plan for a Cooperative Economic Democracy and a Party to Promote the Plan" (Iowa: U.S. Farm News).
    - Morning Star Faith church., no date.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 14)
      Promotional flyer.
    - National Poetry Festival., 1962.; 11 items. (Box 124, Folder 15)
      Clippings and printed materials.
    - Nations, Opal L., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 16)
      Booklet of poems entitled, The Fat Wing Lung Company Poems.
    - New York State Council on the Arts., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 1)
      Annual report.
    - Octavio Paz Conference., 1971.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Payerle, George., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 3)
      Alpha Bathing (Kanchenjunga broadsheet no. 4).
    - Perchik, Simon., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 4)
      Pamphlet of photography and poetry by Perchik and Laurence Shustak.
    - Planning and Conservation League., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 5)
      Legislative program.
    - Pleasants, Ben., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 6)
      Booklet of poetry entitled. 53 Stations of the Tokaido.
    - Poetry Therapy Institute., 1973.; 3 items. (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Politics., no date.; ca. 100 items. (Box 125, Folder 8)
      Invitation cards to benefit Politics (magazine).
    - Poverty., 1964.; ca. 20 items. (Box 125, Folder 9)
      Clippings and printed materials about poverty in California.
    - Press releases and announcements., 1958-1974.; ca. 75 items. (Box 125, Folder 10)
      Assorted press releases and announcements sent to the Rexroths.
    - Prospectuses., 1952-1969.; ca. 75 items. (Box 125, Folder 11)
      Assorted prospectuses for authors, periodicals, and books.
    - Puette, William J., no date.; 2 items. (Box 125, Folder 12)
      Mimeographed booklets of poetry.
    - Radical Education Project., 1966.; 5 items. (Box 125, Folder 13)
      Packet of materials.
    - Reed, Richard L., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 125, Folder 14)
      Oversize sheet of poetry and copies of letters to Las Vegas authorities.
    - Republican Centennial Convention., 1956.; 4 items. (Box 125, Folder 15)
      Press card from The Nation, ticket and a medal.
    - Rexroth, Kenneth--Publicity., ca. 1940-1970.; ca. 150 items. (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
      Assorted print advertising material for Rexroth's books, lectures, and poetry readings.
    - Rexroth Sixtieth Birthday Committee., 1965-1966.; ca. 50 items. (Box 126, Folder 4)
      Correspondence and notes documenting Carol Tinker's planning and execution of Rexroth's 60th birthday celebration.
    - Rockefeller Foundation., 1966-1968.; 2 items. (Box 126, Folder 5)
      President's five-year review and annual report; quarterly report.
    - Roskolenko, Harry., no date.; 1 item. (Box 126, Folder 6)
      Poem, Areas of conscience.
    - Salter, John., 1941.; 13 items. (Box 126, Folder 7)
      Clippings, slides, and photographs of Salter's work at the Chapel of Nuestra Señora de las Rocas.
    - San Domenico Lower School., 1968 April.; 1 item. (Box 126, Folder 8)
      Book of student poetry, entitled Eternity's Sunrise.
    - San Francisco Art Institute., 1964.; 10 items. (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Arts Commission., 1953 September.; 1 item. (Box 127, Folder 2)
      Program for the 7th annual arts festival.
    - San Francisco Arts Resource Development Committee., 1966.; ca. 20 items. (Box 127, Folder 3)
      Assorted printed materials, including reports and clippings.
    - San Francisco Opera., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 127, Folder 4)
      Program.
    - San Francisco Planning Commission., 1965 March.; 1 item. (Box 127, Folder 5)
      Statement by E. Robert Scrofani.
    - San Francisco State College Poetry Center., 1954-1957.; 24 items. (Box 127, Folder 6)
      Announcements, publications, and printed material.
    - Santa Barbara Botanic Garden., 1970.; 3 items. (Box 127, Folder 7)
      Assorted printed material.
    - Savory, Teo., 1967 December.; 1 item. (Box 127, Folder 8)
      A Christmas Message Received During a Car Ride (Christmas greeting, Unicorn Press).
    - School prospectuses., ca. 1956-1960.; 15 items. (Box 127, Folder 9)
      Assorted programs and advertisements for study and retreat programs.
    - Selective service., 1940-1946.; 12 items. (Box 127, Folder 10)
      Assorted print materials regarding the selective service (draft) and conscientious objector status.
    - Sheridan, Author., no date.; 1 item. (Box 127, Folder 11)
      Campaign poster. See box 159 for a flattened copy.
    - Sierra Club., 1963-1971.; 17 items. (Box 127, Folder 12)
      Assorted chapter newsletters and printed materials.
    - Smokey the Bear Sutra., no date.; 1 item. (Box 127, Folder 13)
      Poetry broadside.
    - Stanford University School of Medicine., 1956.; 5 items. (Box 127, Folder 14)
      Lecture series on the philosophical basis of medicine.
    - Stern, Bert., 1950.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 1)
      "Three Poems."
    - Summerhill Society., 1964-1965.; 2 items. (Box 128, Folder 2)
      Statement of policy and packet of poetry, presumably by students.
    - Teatro de la Esperanza., 1972.; 5 items. (Box 128, Folder 3)
      Chicano theater materials.
    - Textile Workers Union of America., 1960-1962.; 10 items. (Box 128, Folder 4)
      Assorted printed materials, plus a letter from Solomon Barkin, director of research for the Union.
    - University of Arizona Rutho Stephan Poetry Center., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 5)
      Brochure.
    - University of Wisconsin., 1964.; 25 items. (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Vangelisti, Paul., 1973.; 2 items. (Box 128, Folder 7)
      "Air" (printed by the Red Hill Press as a supplement to the Invisible City).
    - Vietnam conflict., 1965-1966.; 15 items. (Box 128, Folder 8)
      Assorted materials on Vietnam, Vietnam Day, and the Christian Anti- communism Crusade, including a signed speech by Laurence Ferlinghetti.
    - Watanabe, Takenobu., no date.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 9)
      Self-published poetry.
    - Wilde, John., 1964 September.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 10)
      Transcript of Wilde's radio interview with four wine specialists.
    - Williams, Jonathan (Publisher)., 1964-1974.; 3 items. (Box 128, Folder 11)
      Assorted printed materials, including memorial program for T. Ben Williams.
    - Williams, William Carlos., 1974 December.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 12)
      Christmas Broadside no. 7, published by the Friends of the Lockwood Memorial Library of SUNY, Buffalo.